promised I would make two videos today
to catch myself up so this is video
number 26 I don't know what I'm talking
about I didn't do much mic it minutes
today didn't meditate inside to its to
see what it feels like John meditate for
a day and I had tons of cleaning up to
do around the house do you feel a little
off but not necessarily something I
think that meditation would apologize
also I'm just feeling as per usual lost
like how do I get this idea out there
I've been spending an hour a day typing
and discussing the try to figure out how
to explain the global cooperative and I
don't know just like it's a roller
coaster up and down a feeling not
adequate not like like I'm not the right
person to be doing it
who's supposed to do it I don't know and
being empowered and feeling like yes
this is my purpose on the planet I mean
my child whatever she shouldn't would I
mean whatever she's asked but she
doesn't need to be asked she tells
everyone that my like that I'm saving
the world but that's my job my job is
saving the world
so and I love it when she does that it's
also a little bit embarrassing we pick
up garbage which I don't know if she
thinks that's what I do all day but hey
the four-year-old I can you know I'll be
hero doing that but greatly concerns me
the world only me into her and need to
at least get this information out there
so I can feel like I've done everything
that I can do even if it doesn't go
anywhere but also not with that attitude
feeling like it should go somewhere that
I should be willing to do whatever it
takes to make it go somewhere and so
yeah just sitting here in that I have
another like 10 minutes until the
possibility of my child being dropped
off and she's usually late so I will be
sitting here planning when I'm gonna
write tonight when I do my hours I'm
done my hour but my kitchens basically
cleaning my child's rooms clean in my
living room is clean so accomplishments
and I got tellest
you get me back my old deal or they will
pay me back No Deal
which took over an hour and a bit on the
phone so yeh that's always difficult for
me I hate but and I don't like the
engines today so going for suit the
cohousing and then heading home and just
so grateful that with it weather
changing I get soup because that sounds
amazing
today a little chilly it feels like fall
weather and that I didn't have to cook
it is the first co-host and every time I
take a week off I just I'm just so
grateful that it exists and then I'm a
part of it and also figuring out ways to
feel blessed and honor that and also
make the rest of the world get those
same amazing opportunities to eat
healthy food and eat with community and
not have to cook and clean every night
and not have it be necessarily something
like a soup kitchen which comes with a
theoretically a lack of dignity where
there's better solutions and I'm
listening into the soul of money and
that's inspiring me as well and so I
can't leave always talking about three
and a half minutes because it seems like
I'm done no I'm done all right well
buddy have a good Monday tomorrow I will
resume video 27 and I will stay on track
all right